Today is a great day. Why? Because today is Stan Lee Zupnick Day. This is a great
moment not only for our engineering school, the Clark School, but the entire
university and the surrounding community. This is a great investment. It's a great
investment that the state is happy to be involved with because it's going to
change lives. It's going to change the way we live, the generations live. Zupnick Hall
will be a new place for engineering students to call home, a place to learn,
to grow, and for students to meet and inspire one another. To emulate the
Terrapin, stick our necks out and keep moving forward. Achieving that ambition
means creating an environment that's right for innovation, collaboration,
diversity, inclusion, where engineers and non-engineers synergistically connect to
find solutions at work. Education remains the most potent force in our country
to change lives. By bringing together different departments and centers, our
already stellar engineering curriculum will become even stronger. This is one
more fantastic addition as we continue to build out the capital of quantum. This
new building is the last piece of the Clark Foundation's building together
investment at the university and it's a wonderful capstone to our partnership
with Maryland. Together our investments will cultivate the next generation of
engineering leaders. Today, more than ever, our students and engineers in general
must have vision. It is my hope that this new space will make it easier to
exchange ideas. Having such dedicated friends and partners is a big reason why
I'm optimistic about where our campus is today and where it's headed in our
future. Three, two, one. It's not enough to just be fearless anymore. We also have
to move fearlessly forward.